{
  "LevelId": 1,
  "Questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "level_image": 3,
      "answer_text": "BUDGET",
      "question": "What is a financial plan that estimates income and expenditures over a certain period?"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "level_image": 3,
      "answer_text": "FRIEND",
      "question": "Who is a person you have a close and trusting relationship with?"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "level_image": 3,
      "answer_text": "DOCTOR",
      "question": "Who is trained to diagnose and treat illnesses and injuries?"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "level_image": 3,
      "answer_text": "BATTLE",
      "question": "A conflict between opposing forces is known as"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "level_image": 3,
      "answer_text": "CLIENT",
      "question": "Who seeks the services or advice of a professional or business"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "level_image": 3,
      "answer_text": "FLOWER",
      "question": "What colorful and fragrant symbol of nature is often given on special occasions"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "level_image": 3,
      "answer_text": "IGNORE",
      "question": "What is the opposite of paying attention to"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "level_image": 3,
      "answer_text": "BEAKER",
      "question": "What is a cylindrical container with a flat bottom, used in laboratories for holding liquids"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "level_image": 3,
      "answer_text": "AIRBAG",
      "question": "In a car, what safety device inflates upon impact to protect the occupants"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "level_image": 3,
      "answer_text": "FLYING",
      "question": "What is the action of moving through the air, typically with wings or in an aircraft"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "level_image": 0,
      "answer_text": "DICTIONARY",
      "question": "What is a reference book that provides definitions and explanations of words"
    }
  ]
}